var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "yatiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْتِهِ",
        "answer": "We give him",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "nu'tihi",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are given",
        "pcklId": "493",
        "tlit": "ūtītum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِثْمِ",
        "answer": "sins",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-ith'mi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرًا",
        "answer": "any payment",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَجْرُهُ",
        "answer": "then his reward",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "fa-ajruhu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلٍ",
        "answer": "a term",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ajalin",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "have they taken",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter ",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْذَنْ",
        "answer": "Allah has given permission of it",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yadhan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِهِ",
        "answer": "by His permission",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nihi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "until",
        "pcklId": "468",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "469",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "470",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "471",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "1148",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1149",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِي",
        "answer": "and that which",
        "pcklId": "1150",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1151",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1152",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1153",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1154",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "1155",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1156",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1157",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is of) which",
        "pcklId": "1158",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1159",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1160",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1161",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1162",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1163",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "1164",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1165",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1166",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1167",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1168",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1169",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) those who",
        "pcklId": "1170",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One",
        "pcklId": "1171",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2387",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2388",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2389",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah willed",
        "pcklId": "2390",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "But Allah ",
        "pcklId": "2391",
        "tlit": "fal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2392",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2393",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2394",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has sent down",
        "pcklId": "2395",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2396",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2397",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2398",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2399",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2400",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has given permission of it",
        "pcklId": "2401",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah gives glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "2402",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2403",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2404",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah willed",
        "pcklId": "2405",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah eliminates",
        "pcklId": "2406",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah extends",
        "pcklId": "2407",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2408",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2409",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2410",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "2411",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2412",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "2413",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2414",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "To Allah",
        "pcklId": "2415",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah should speak to him",
        "pcklId": "2416",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2417",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2418",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "608",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَى",
        "answer": "and to",
        "pcklId": "609",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "610",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "(is) to",
        "pcklId": "611",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "612",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "613",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to it",
        "pcklId": "614",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "for Himself",
        "pcklId": "615",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Himself",
        "pcklId": "616",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "617",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "618",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "(there) for",
        "pcklId": "619",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "620",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "621",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "To",
        "pcklId": "622",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "ami",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِرْتَ",
        "answer": "you are commanded",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "umir'ta",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمِرْتُ",
        "answer": "and I am commanded",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "wa-umir'tu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمْرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their affairs",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "wa-amruhum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُمُورِ",
        "answer": "matters of determination",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "l-umūri",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Command",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "amrinā",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُمُورُ",
        "answer": "all affairs",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "l-umūru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّ",
        "answer": "(the) mother",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "umma",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةً",
        "answer": "a community",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "ummatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنْتُ",
        "answer": "I believe",
        "pcklId": "450",
        "tlit": "āmantu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "451",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "452",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "453",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "454",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "455",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "456",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "457",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِيمَانُ",
        "answer": "the faith",
        "pcklId": "636",
        "tlit": "l-īmānu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِنَاثًا",
        "answer": "females",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ināthan",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِنَاثًا",
        "answer": "and females",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wa-ināthan",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانَ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-insāna",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانَ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-insāna",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their families",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlīhim",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Signs",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Signs",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "surely (are) Signs",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "laāyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَثَّ",
        "answer": "He has dispersed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "batha",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْسُطُ",
        "answer": "He extends",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yabsuṭu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَسَطَ",
        "answer": "Allah extends",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "basaṭa",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَشِّرُ",
        "answer": "Allah gives glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yubashiru",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَشَرٍ",
        "answer": "for any human",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "libasharin",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "the All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "l-baṣīru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَاطِلَ",
        "answer": "the falsehood",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-bāṭila",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "baʿdihim",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِ",
        "answer": "after Him",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "baʿdihi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعِيدٍ",
        "answer": "far",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "baʿīdin",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبَغَوْا",
        "answer": "surely they would rebel",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "labaghaw",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَبْغُونَ",
        "answer": "and rebel",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wayabghūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْيًا",
        "answer": "(out of) rivalry",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "baghyan",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَغْيُ",
        "answer": "tyranny",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-baghyu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "and more lasting",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-abqā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَلَاغُ",
        "answer": "the conveyance",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-balāghu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among them",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمُ",
        "answer": "between you",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "baynakumu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَنَا",
        "answer": "between us",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "baynanā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَكُمُ",
        "answer": "and between you",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "wabaynakumu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَنَا",
        "answer": "[between] us",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "baynanā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among them",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعْ",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿ",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوْبَةَ",
        "answer": "the repentance",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-tawbata",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْتَبِي",
        "answer": "chooses",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yajtabī",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجَادِلُونَ",
        "answer": "dispute",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yujādilūna",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَوَارِ",
        "answer": "(are) the ships",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-jawāri",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(The) recompense",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "wajazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَجَعَلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "He could have made them",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "lajaʿalahum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "He made",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَجْعَلُ",
        "answer": "and He makes",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "wayajʿalu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have made it",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْمَعُ",
        "answer": "will assemble",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yajmaʿu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَمْعِ",
        "answer": "(of) Assembly",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-jamʿi",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمْعِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their gathering",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "jamʿihim",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْتَنِبُونَ",
        "answer": "avoid",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yajtanibūna",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Gardens",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-janāti",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتُجِيبَ",
        "answer": "response has been made to Him",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "us'tujība",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَجِيبُ",
        "answer": "And He answers",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wayastajību",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَجَابُوا",
        "answer": "respond",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "is'tajābū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَجِيبُوا",
        "answer": "Respond",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "is'tajībū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمُ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "jāahumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "like",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجَابٍ",
        "answer": "a veil",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥijābin",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَاجُّونَ",
        "answer": "argue",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yuḥājjūna",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُجَّةَ",
        "answer": "argument",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ḥujjata",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُجَّتُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their argument",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ḥujjatuhum",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرْثَ",
        "answer": "(the) harvest",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥartha",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرْثِهِ",
        "answer": "his harvest",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ḥarthihi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرْثَ",
        "answer": "(the) harvest",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥartha",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُسْنًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "ḥus'nan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنَةً",
        "answer": "any good",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "ḥasanatan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَفِيظًا",
        "answer": "(as) a guardian",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ḥafīẓan",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَفِيظٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a Guardian",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ḥafīẓun",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُحِقُّ",
        "answer": "and establishes",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wayuḥiqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the truth",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "right",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَحُكْمُهُ",
        "answer": "then its ruling",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "faḥuk'muhu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Wise",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَمْدِ",
        "answer": "(the) praise",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "biḥamdi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمِيدُ",
        "answer": "the Praiseworthy",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamīdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلَهَا",
        "answer": "(is) around it",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ḥawlahā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحِيصٍ",
        "answer": "place of refuge",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "maḥīṣin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "gives life",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "(for) the life",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "khabīrun",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْتِمْ",
        "answer": "He would seal",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yakhtim",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسِرُوا",
        "answer": "lost",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khasirū",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاشِعِينَ",
        "answer": "humbled",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "khāshiʿīna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَفِيٍّ",
        "answer": "stealthy",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "khafiyyin",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْتَلَفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you differ",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "ikh'talaftum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقُ",
        "answer": "He creates",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "yakhluqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقُ",
        "answer": "(is the) creation",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "khalqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَابَّةٍ",
        "answer": "(the) creatures",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "dābbatin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَاحِضَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) invalid",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "dāḥiḍatun",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُدْخِلُ",
        "answer": "He admits",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "yud'khilu",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْرِي",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tadrī",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُدْرِيكَ",
        "answer": "will make you know",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yud'rīka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you call them",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "tadʿūhum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَادْعُ",
        "answer": "then invite",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "fa-ud'ʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "the religion",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينَ",
        "answer": "the religion",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-dīna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "the religion",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذْرَؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "He multiplies you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yadhra-ukum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذُّكُورَ",
        "answer": "[the] males",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "l-dhukūra",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكْرَانًا",
        "answer": "males",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "dhuk'rānan",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذُّلِّ",
        "answer": "disgrace",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-dhuli",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We cause to taste",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "adhaqnā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَى",
        "answer": "You will see",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَى",
        "answer": "And you will see",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "watarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَوُا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "ra-awū",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And you will see them",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "watarāhum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "753",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "754",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "755",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "(is) our Lord",
        "pcklId": "756",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your Lord",
        "pcklId": "757",
        "tlit": "warabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "758",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "759",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "760",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "to their Lord",
        "pcklId": "761",
        "tlit": "lirabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "to your Lord",
        "pcklId": "762",
        "tlit": "lirabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "raḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتَهُ",
        "answer": "His mercy",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "raḥmatahu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "Mercy",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "raḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَدٍّ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "maraddin",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَدَّ",
        "answer": "averting",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "maradda",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْزُقُ",
        "answer": "He gives provision",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yarzuqu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We have provided them",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "razaqnāhum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّزْقَ",
        "answer": "the provision",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-riz'qa",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّزْقَ",
        "answer": "the provision",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-riz'qa",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We have sent you",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "arsalnāka",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْسِلَ",
        "answer": "(by) sending",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "yur'sila",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a messenger",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَوَاكِدَ",
        "answer": "motionless",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "rawākida",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُوحًا",
        "answer": "an inspiration",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "rūḥan",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّيحَ",
        "answer": "He can cause the wind to become still",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-rīḥa",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "desiring",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "desiring",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَوْضَاتِ",
        "answer": "flowering meadows",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "rawḍāti",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَيْبَ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "rayba",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُرِيبٍ",
        "answer": "disquieting",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "murībin",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُزَوِّجُهُمْ",
        "answer": "He grants them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuzawwijuhum",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجًا",
        "answer": "mates",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "azwājan",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجًا",
        "answer": "mates",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "azwājan",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزِدْ",
        "answer": "We increase",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "nazid",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزِدْ",
        "answer": "We increase",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "nazid",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَزِيدُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and increases (for) them",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "wayazīduhum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْأَلُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I ask you",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "asalukum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَبِّحُونَ",
        "answer": "glorify",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yusabbiḥūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقَتْ",
        "answer": "(that) preceded",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "sabaqat",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلٍ",
        "answer": "way",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "sabīlin",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلُ",
        "answer": "the way",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "l-sabīlu",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلٍ",
        "answer": "way",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "sabīlin",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلٍ",
        "answer": "way",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "sabīlin",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّعِيرِ",
        "answer": "the Blazing Fire",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-saʿīri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْكِنِ",
        "answer": "He can cause the wind to become still",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yus'kini",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتُ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "l-samāwātu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَمًّى",
        "answer": "specified",
        "pcklId": "374",
        "tlit": "musamman",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) an evil",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "sayyi-atin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) an evil",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "sayyi-atun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَةٌ",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "sayyi-atun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّيِّئَاتِ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-sayiāti",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةَ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿata",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿati",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدٌ",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "shadīdun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدٌ",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "shadīdun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرَعَ",
        "answer": "He has ordained",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sharaʿa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرَعُوا",
        "answer": "who have ordained",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sharaʿū",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) partners",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "shurakāu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) fearful",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mush'fiqūna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْفِقِينَ",
        "answer": "fearful",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "mush'fiqīna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَكُورٌ",
        "answer": "All-Appreciative",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "shakūrun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَكُورٍ",
        "answer": "(and) grateful",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "shakūrin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَكٍّ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "shakkin",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُورَىٰ",
        "answer": "(are conducted by) consultation",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shūrā",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "Allah willed",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُونَ",
        "answer": "they wish",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "yashāūna",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَإِ",
        "answer": "Allah willed",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "yasha-i",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَأْ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "yasha",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We will",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "461",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "a thing",
        "pcklId": "462",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٌ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "463",
        "tlit": "shayon",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "a thing",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَرَ",
        "answer": "(is) patient",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ṣabara",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَّارٍ",
        "answer": "patient",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "ṣabbārin",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّدُورِ",
        "answer": "(is in) the breasts",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-ṣudūri",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "(the) Path",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطِ",
        "answer": "(The) path",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭi",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْلَحَ",
        "answer": "and makes reconciliation",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣlaḥa",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "prayer",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصَابَكُمْ",
        "answer": "befalls you",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "aṣābakum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصَابَهُمُ",
        "answer": "strikes them",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "aṣābahumu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصِبْهُمْ",
        "answer": "befalls them",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "tuṣib'hum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصِيبَةٍ",
        "answer": "(the) misfortune",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "muṣībatin",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "reach",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taṣīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "(is) the final return",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-maṣīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضْلِلِ",
        "answer": "Allah lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "yuḍ'lili",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضْلِلِ",
        "answer": "Allah lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "yuḍ'lili",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "error",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَرْفٍ",
        "answer": "a glance",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṭarfin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَظْلَلْنَ",
        "answer": "then they would remain",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fayaẓlalna",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "oppress",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "yaẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلْمِهِ",
        "answer": "he has been wronged",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "ẓul'mihi",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "And the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "wal-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهْرِهِ",
        "answer": "its back",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ẓahrihi",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "with His slaves",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "biʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَهُ",
        "answer": "(to) His slaves ",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "ʿibādahu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His slaves",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِعِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "for His slaves",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "liʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "of His slaves",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "biʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِنَا",
        "answer": "Our slaves",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "ʿibādinā",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُعْجِزِينَ",
        "answer": "(can) escape",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "bimuʿ'jizīna",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَعْجِلُ",
        "answer": "Seek to hasten",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yastaʿjilu",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَعْدِلَ",
        "answer": "that I do justice",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "li-aʿdila",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is a) punishment",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَبِيًّا",
        "answer": "(in) Arabic",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ʿarabiyyan",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْرَضُونَ",
        "answer": "being exposed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'raḍūna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرَضُوا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "aʿraḍū",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزْمِ",
        "answer": "matters of determination",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ʿazmi",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Great",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْفُو",
        "answer": "and pardons",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wayaʿfū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْفُو",
        "answer": "But He pardons",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wayaʿfū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْفُ",
        "answer": "but He pardons",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wayaʿfu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَفَا",
        "answer": "pardons",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ʿafā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَقِيمًا",
        "answer": "barren",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ʿaqīman",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "and know",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "wayaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "and He knows",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "wayaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "And may know",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "wayaʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالْأَعْلَامِ",
        "answer": "like [the] mountains",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "kal-aʿlāmi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمُ",
        "answer": "the knowledge",
        "pcklId": "640",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'mu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "747",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "810",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "811",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the Most High",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaliyu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) Most High",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ʿaliyyun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُنَا",
        "answer": "our deeds",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "aʿmālunā",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your deeds",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "aʿmālukum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضِبُوا",
        "answer": "they are angry",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ghaḍibū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضَبٌ",
        "answer": "(is) wrath",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ghaḍabun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْفِرُونَ",
        "answer": "forgive",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yaghfirūna",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَفَرَ",
        "answer": "and forgives",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "waghafara",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَغْفِرُونَ",
        "answer": "and ask for forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "wayastaghfirūna",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَفُورُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-ghafūru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْثَ",
        "answer": "the rain",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-ghaytha",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفَوَاحِشَ",
        "answer": "and the immoralities",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-fawāḥisha",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِحَ",
        "answer": "he rejoices",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fariḥa",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَفَرَّقُوا",
        "answer": "be divided",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "tatafarraqū",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفَرَّقُوا",
        "answer": "they became divided",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "tafarraqū",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقٌ",
        "answer": "A party",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "farīqun",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَرِيقٌ",
        "answer": "and a party",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wafarīqun",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "He has invented",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "if'tarā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَصْلِ",
        "answer": "decisive",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-faṣli",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَضْلُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Bounty",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-faḍlu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Bounty",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَفَطَّرْنَ",
        "answer": "break up",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yatafaṭṭarna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاطِرُ",
        "answer": "(The) Creator",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fāṭiru",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "tafʿalūna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقِهِنَّ",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fawqihinna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْبَلُ",
        "answer": "accepts",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yaqbalu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you ",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْدِرُ",
        "answer": "and restricts",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wayaqdiru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَدَرٍ",
        "answer": "in (due) measure",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "biqadarin",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّمَتْ",
        "answer": "have sent forth",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "qaddamat",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْآنًا",
        "answer": "a Quran",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "qur'ānan",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "the relatives",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-qur'bā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبٌ",
        "answer": "(is) near",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "qarībun",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْتَرِفْ",
        "answer": "earns",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaqtarif",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the towns",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقُضِيَ",
        "answer": "surely, it (would have) been settled",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "laquḍiya",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقُضِيَ",
        "answer": "surely, it (would have) been judged",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "laquḍiya",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلْبِكَ",
        "answer": "your heart",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "qalbika",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقَالِيدُ",
        "answer": "(the) keys",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "maqālīdu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَنَطُوا",
        "answer": "they have despaired",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "qanaṭū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْ",
        "answer": "but say",
        "pcklId": "1419",
        "tlit": "waqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1420",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) they say",
        "pcklId": "1421",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "saying",
        "pcklId": "1422",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And will say",
        "pcklId": "1423",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "establish",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "aqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "wa-aqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَقِمْ",
        "answer": "and stand firm",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "wa-is'taqim",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "549",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "lasting",
        "pcklId": "618",
        "tlit": "muqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "Straight",
        "pcklId": "639",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Strong",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-qawiyu",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبُرَ",
        "answer": "Is difficult",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kabura",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَبِيرُ",
        "answer": "the Great",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "l-kabīru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبَائِرَ",
        "answer": "(the) greater",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "kabāira",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٍ",
        "answer": "(the) Book",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "kitābin",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابُ",
        "answer": "the Book (is)",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "l-kitābu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرٍ",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "kathīrin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرٍ",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "kathīrin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبُوا",
        "answer": "they earned",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "kasabū",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "have earned",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "kasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبُوا",
        "answer": "they have earned",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "kasabū",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) ungrateful",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "kafūrun",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْكَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "And the disbelievers ",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "wal-kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "for everyone",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَلِّمَهُ",
        "answer": "Allah should speak to him",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yukallimahu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكَلِمَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "by His Words",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "bikalimātihi",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةٌ",
        "answer": "(for) a word",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "kalimatun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةُ",
        "answer": "(for) a word",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "kalimatu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكَادُ",
        "answer": "Almost",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "takādu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "1147",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "1148",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "will be",
        "pcklId": "1149",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "1150",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "(did) you",
        "pcklId": "1151",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلْجَإٍ",
        "answer": "refuge",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "malja-in",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَطِيفٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Subtle",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "laṭīfun",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "(There) is not",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَتَاعُ",
        "answer": "(is) but a passing enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "famatāʿu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمِثْلِهِ",
        "answer": "like Him",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "kamith'lihi",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُهَا",
        "answer": "like it",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "mith'luhā",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَمْحُ",
        "answer": "And Allah eliminates",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wayamḥu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُمَارُونَ",
        "answer": "dispute",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yumārūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(belongs the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "and the Angels",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "wal-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "(to) the dead",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُنْذِرَ",
        "answer": "that you may warn",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "litundhira",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُنْذِرَ",
        "answer": "and warn",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "watundhira",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزِّلُ",
        "answer": "He sends down",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "yunazzilu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزِّلُ",
        "answer": "sends down",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yunazzilu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "Allah has sent down",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "(has) sent down",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْشُرُ",
        "answer": "and spreads",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wayanshuru",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيبٍ",
        "answer": "share",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "naṣībin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْصُرُونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(who) will help them",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yanṣurūnahum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْتَصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "defend themselves",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "yantaṣirūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْتَصَرَ",
        "answer": "defends himself",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "intaṣara",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرٍ",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "naṣīrin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرٍ",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "naṣīrin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "looking",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْعَامِ",
        "answer": "the cattle",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-anʿāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they spend",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكِيرٍ",
        "answer": "denial",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nakīrin",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنِيبُ",
        "answer": "I turn",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "unību",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنِيبُ",
        "answer": "turns",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yunību",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورًا",
        "answer": "a light",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "nūran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَهْدِي",
        "answer": "and guides",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "wayahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَهْدِي",
        "answer": "We guide",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "nahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَهْدِي",
        "answer": "surely guide",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "latahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their desires",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ahwāahum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوبِقْهُنَّ",
        "answer": "He could destroy them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yūbiq'hunna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحِي",
        "answer": "reveals",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yūḥī",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We have revealed",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We have revealed",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "then he reveals",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "fayūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We have revealed",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحْيًا",
        "answer": "(by) revelation",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "waḥyan",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوَدَّةَ",
        "answer": "the love",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-mawadata",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُورِثُوا",
        "answer": "were made to inherit",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ūrithū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَاءِ",
        "answer": "behind",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "warāi",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمِيزَانَ",
        "answer": "and the Balance",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wal-mīzāna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَّىٰ",
        "answer": "He enjoined",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waṣṣā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَّيْنَا",
        "answer": "We enjoined",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waṣṣaynā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاقِعٌ",
        "answer": "(will) befall",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wāqiʿun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَكَّلْتُ",
        "answer": "I put my trust",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "tawakkaltu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَكَّلُونَ",
        "answer": "put (their) trust",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yatawakkalūna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوَكِيلٍ",
        "answer": "a manager",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "biwakīlin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "protectors",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٍّ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "waliyyin",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "protectors",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَلِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the Protector",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "l-waliyu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَلِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the Protector",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "l-waliyu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٍّ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "waliyyin",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٍّ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "waliyyin",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهَبُ",
        "answer": "He grants",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yahabu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَهَبُ",
        "answer": "and He grants",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wayahabu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hands",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "aydīkum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(of the) Day",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "a Day",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "yawmun",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "42",
        "ayah": "47"
    }
]; 
export default words;